<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">Jetlagged and Confused</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://jetlaggedandconfused.com/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://jetlaggedandconfused.com" />
<updated>2015-11-02T08:27:55+01:00</updated>
<id>http://jetlaggedandconfused.com/</id>
<author>
  <name>Cara and Mike</name>
  <uri>http://jetlaggedandconfused.com/</uri>
  <email>mikeandcarawedding@gmail.com</email>
</author>


  

<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Adventures in Paris, Week One]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://jetlaggedandconfused.com/blog/adventures-in-paris-week-one/" />
  <id>http://jetlaggedandconfused.com/blog/adventures-in-paris-week-one</id>
  <published>2015-11-01T11:09:56+01:00</published>
  <updated>2015-11-01T11:09:56+01:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>Cara and Mike</name>
    <uri>http://jetlaggedandconfused.com</uri>
    <email>mikeandcarawedding@gmail.com</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">
    &lt;p&gt;So my darling husband is in the habit of dropping me off in a foreign country
and then leaving two or three days later. Which is once again the case as he’s
been in DC all week on business. (Yes, I understand that I’m getting to live in
Paris, so pity will be hard to come by.)  The good news is we found an
apartment and hope to move in on Monday before Mike leaves, again, this time
for Ottawa. It will be such a relief to no longer be living out of a suitcase.
The apartment is super cute and very Parisian – with an an office and a
guest room. We’ll have to become far more stylish just to live in it, but
it’s Paris, so anything is possible, right? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;centered&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015.11.02/apartment.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for Mike, he’s seen more of DC in the past week, and even more of the inside
of a Boeing 767 and is generally confused about what time zone he’s in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half centered&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015.11.02/selfie.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On my end, one of the first orders of business is to try to learn the language.
At least enough to make it look like I’m trying. Because the French love
Americans who can’t talk French. ESPECIALLY Parisians.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015.11.02/river.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My intention is to learn a new word or phrase daily and test it out in a real
world setting. Today’s modest goal - feeding myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015.11.02/paul-window.jpg&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The cutest little bakery, Paul Pâtissier, is only a few blocks from where we’ve
been staying in the second arrondissement. It’s cruel how Paul taunts you with
beautiful tartlettes aux pommes in the window and the smell of croissants au
chocolat wafting halfway down the block. Mercifully, I have yet to learn the
phrase, “I’ll take one of everything.” &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m happy to report I SUCCESSFULLY ordered a chicken salad and canelé – in
FRENCH!  And by successful, I mean that I let about five people go in front of
me, pretending to be indecisive but really waiting until other customers left,
lest there be an audience to witness my first attempt (failure) at speaking a
language I know precious little of. I uttered a few phrases that maybe,
possibly sounded French, pointed at items behind the window counter and the
nice man handed me my dinner. Victory!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thinking I’d add some additional protein to the meal, I set out to find
sardines at the Franprix down the street. Apparently, the French can squeeze an
impressive number of canned items into one tiny city market. I found one that
looked like sardines, but there’s a 50-50 chance I’m now eating cat food.
Surely French cats eat well, no?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;centered&quot;&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;/images/2015.11.02/sardines.png&quot; /&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://jetlaggedandconfused.com/blog/adventures-in-paris-week-one/&quot;&gt;Adventures in Paris, Week One&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Cara and Mike at &lt;a href=&quot;http://jetlaggedandconfused.com&quot;&gt;Jetlagged and Confused&lt;/a&gt; on November 01, 2015.&lt;/p&gt;
  </content>
</entry>

</feed>